

Muhammad AdhiNugroho

Mobile Developer

**** 087771210204

adzkiyadzikrullah@gmail.com

Bekasi Utara, Jawa Barat

in Muhammad AdhiNugroho

ZoD3V

EXPERIENCE

Webinar UI UX Career Opportunity to be a UI/UX Designer Webinar in ecampuz

01/2021 - Present

- Learn what is UI/UX
- How Important is the Role of UI/UX?
- Important Skills & Tips to Become a UI/UX Designer
- Learn Wireframing and Prototyping, Mockup

Website Developer Internship

Solidarity Care

01/2022 - 04/2022

- Markup and web languages such as HTML,CSS and Javascript
- Make a solidarity care dashboard for company
- Make database for company
- Make User Interface Web Design
- Implement API
- Make User interface Kit Design
- Make User interface Prototype
- asynchronous request and ajax
- Search engine optimisation
- Security

IDN Teaching

React Trainer

11/2021 - 11/2021

- Teaching React at Jakarta global university for 3 days
- Fixing error for participation
- Make Simple Project with React JS

EDUCATION

Software Engineer

IDN Boarding School

2023

Vocational High School

- Make a swift tutorial book for beginners
- UI UX Design Competetion SIFESTUBL2021

SUMMARY

I'm a high school student majoring in RPL, with android, IOS, website and UI design skills with 1 year experience.

I'm from North Bekasi, born in 2004, I started coding at the age of 15, more precisely when I was still in vocational high school.

SKILLS

Kotlin Intermediate Advanced Flutter PHP Advanced Intermediate MySQL HTML Intermediate CSS Intermediate Intermediate Javascript React JS Intermediate Intermediate Swift Advanced Figma

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate

CERTIFICATES

Learn SOLID programming principles at Dicoding 12/2021 - 12/2024

Get started programming with kotlin at Dicoding 12/2021 - 12/2024

Learn to make android apps for beginners at Dicoding 09/2021 - 09/2024

Creating iOS apps for beginners at Dicoding 06/2021 - 06/2024